{
    "subject": "resource/Matti_Manushulu",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Indian_films",
    "human_readable": "Matti Manushulu is a subject of Indian films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9649592638015747,
            "question": "Is Matti Manushulu known for acting in Indian cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9473384618759155,
            "question": "What is Matti Manushulu's role in Indian film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9189173579216003,
            "question": "What are some of the popular genres of Indian films that Matti Manushulu has acted in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8911070227622986,
            "question": "Is Matti Manushulu a well-known actor in India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.86661696434021,
            "question": "In what type of films does Matti Manushulu appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6951078772544861,
            "question": "Can you name any films featuring Matti Manushulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6903311610221863,
            "question": "What nationality is Matti Manushulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6714237928390503,
            "question": "What is Matti Manushulu's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49341079592704773,
            "question": "Where does Matti Manushulu primarily work as an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40119948983192444,
            "question": "Are there any awards or recognitions received by Matti Manushulu?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Matti Manushulu is a subject of Indian films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4742_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Matti Manushulu primarily work as an actor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4742_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Matti Manushulu's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4742_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Matti Manushulu?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4742_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4742_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4742_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4742_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4742_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4742_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4742_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4742_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4742_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4742_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4742_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided supports the statement that \"Matti Manushulu is a subject of Indian films.\" Multiple documents mention this film, including details about its production, awards, and director B. Narsing Rao's contributions to Telugu cinema."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}